(Penny:)Okay, Baby-Doll Pink...
(Penny:)...let's see if you can cover up the fact
that I got my dad's feet.
LEONARD:
It's two degrees, Sheldon.
I just wanna turn up
the thermostat two degrees.
SHELDON: Let me point out
that two degrees can be the difference...
...between water and steam.
LEONARD:
Yes, if we were lived in a tea kettle.
SHELDON: This is the temperature you
agreed to in the roommate agreement.
LEONARD:
Screw the roommate agreement.
SHELDON: No, you don't screw
the roommate agreement...
...the roommate agreement screws you.
LEONARD: You know what,
go to hell and set their thermostat.
SHELDON: I don't have to go to hell.
At 73 degrees, I'm there already.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
(Penny(after a knock on the door):)Who is it?
LEONARD: Leonard.
-Hang on.
(Leonard:)Can I sleep on your couch tonight?
(Penny:)You can try, but the people
across the hall are being very noisy.
(Leonard:)You heard that, huh?
(Penny:)Apparently, the one fella
tried to adjust the thermostat...